{"av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 12:59:50": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 12:59:50", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 12:59:50", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 12:59:51"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:00:05": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:00:05", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:00:05", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:00:06"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:00:20": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:00:20", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:00:20", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:00:21"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:00:35": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:00:35", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:00:35", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:00:36"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:00:50": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:00:50", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:00:50", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:00:51"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:01:05": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:01:05", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:01:05", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:01:06"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:01:20": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:01:20", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:01:20", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:01:21"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:01:35": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:01:35", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:01:35", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:01:36"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:01:50": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:01:50", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:01:50", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:01:51"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:02:15": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:02:15", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:02:15", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:02:15"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:02:30": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:02:30", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:02:30", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:02:30"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:02:45": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:02:45", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:02:45", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:02:45"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:03:00": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:03:00", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:03:00", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:03:00"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:03:15": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:03:15", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:03:15", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:03:15"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:03:30": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:03:30", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:03:30", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:03:30"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:03:45": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:03:45", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:03:45", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:03:45"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:04:00": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:04:00", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:04:00", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:04:00"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:04:15": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:04:15", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:04:15", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:04:15"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:04:30": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:04:30", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:04:30", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:04:30"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:04:45": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:04:45", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:04:45", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:04:45"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:05:00": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:05:00", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:05:00", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:05:00"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:05:15": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:05:15", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:05:15", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:05:15"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:05:30": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:05:30", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:05:30", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:05:30"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:05:45": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:05:45", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:05:45", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:05:45"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:06:00": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:06:00", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:06:00", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:06:00"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:06:15": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:06:15", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:06:15", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:06:15"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:06:30": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:06:30", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:06:30", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:06:30"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:06:45": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:06:45", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:06:45", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:06:45"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:07:00": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:07:00", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:07:00", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:07:00"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:07:15": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:07:15", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:07:15", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:07:15"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:07:30": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:07:30", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:07:30", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:07:30"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:07:45": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:07:45", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:07:45", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:07:45"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:08:00": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:08:00", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:08:00", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:08:00"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:08:15": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:08:15", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:08:15", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:08:15"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:08:30": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:08:30", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:08:30", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:08:30"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:08:45": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:08:45", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:08:45", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:08:45"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:09:00": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:09:00", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:09:00", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:09:00"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:09:15": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:09:15", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:09:15", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:09:15"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:09:30": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:09:30", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:09:30", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:09:30"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:09:45": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:09:45", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:09:45", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:09:45"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:10:00": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:10:00", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:10:00", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:10:00"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:10:15": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:10:15", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:10:15", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:10:15"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:10:30": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:10:30", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:10:30", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:10:30"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:10:45": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:10:45", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:10:45", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:10:45"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:11:00": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:11:00", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:11:00", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:11:00"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:11:15": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:11:15", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:11:15", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:11:15"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:11:30": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:11:30", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:11:30", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:11:30"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:11:45": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:11:45", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:11:45", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:11:45"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:12:00": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:12:00", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:12:00", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:12:00"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:12:15": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:12:15", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:12:15", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:12:15"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:12:30": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:12:30", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:12:30", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:12:30"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:12:45": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:12:45", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:12:45", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:12:45"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:13:00": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:13:00", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:13:00", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:13:00"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:13:15": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:13:15", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:13:15", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:13:15"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:13:30": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:13:30", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:13:30", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:13:30"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:13:45": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:13:45", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:13:45", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:13:45"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:14:00": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:14:00", "entries": [{"question": "", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:14:00", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:14:00"}]}, "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:14:33": {"question_id": "av9lrUTiZjUTDLRFVD97SQQf1cC208/25/2021, 13:14:33", "entries": [{"question": "This book is", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:14:33", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:14:38"}, {"question": "This book is the most important book for Christians", "answer": "", "Timestamp_frontend": "08/25/2021, 13:14:44", "Timestamp_backend": "08/25/2021, 13:14:51"}]}}